parentmail.co.uk 2002-02-07

# LOSTYOU.COM

### About LOSTYOU.COM ™

### Privacy Policy

We take your privacy and data protection seriously, and although this is a contact service that allows registered users to search and view information provided by other registered users about themselves we want to make sure that you know what data we collect and how we use it. 

If you have any questions or queries relating to our privacy policy, please contact [dataprotection@lostyou.com](mailto:dataprotection@lostyou.com). 

### Cookies

LOSTYOU.COM ™ uses session cookies to identify you while you are logged in and using the site. 

When you login our servers send a session cookie to your browser, this cookie is remembered by your browser which sends it back to us every time you look at a page - this is how our servers can work out who you are. 

Unlike many sites, these cookies are NOT stored on your computer and are NOT used to track your usage of the site & when you logout or close your browser window this cookie is either changed by us or forgotten by your computer. 

### Access to your data

LOSTYOU.COM ™ is a contact website, its main purpose it to allow registered users to locate each other by searching information that they have chosen to provide about themselves and their work history. 

Any data added to the site should be considered PUBLIC ACCESS, and by entering data into the system you consent to allowing public access to the information you provide via this website. 

A user can request a copy of all the information we have in our system relating to them for a nominal fee of £10.00, please contact [dataprotection@lostyou.com](mailto:dataprotection@lostyou.com). 

### Personal data required to use the service

This information is required by the system should you choose to register. 

  * Your name. 
  * Email address. 
  * A password. 
  * The version of our Terms & Conditions you agreed to when you registered as a user. 
  * When you last updated your contact information. 
  * The country you live in. 
  * Your permission to receive our email newsletter, email alerts when new users register, and to allow other subscribers to contact you via the website. 

Any workplace records, messages, notices or other records created by a user will include their name and allow registered users to view their personal data. 

### Additional personal data you can choose to provide

All of the following information is strictly optional, although it is not required in order to use the service it will make it easier for people to locate you. 

  * A description of yourself. 
  * The town/city where you live. 
  * Places where you worked, including dates and any comments you chose to make. 
  * Messages that we will forward to other registered users on your behalf. 
  * Messages that you can leave on noticeboards for other registered users to read. 
  * Invitations to register at LOSTYOU.COM ™ that you send to colleagues. 

### Updating your records

A user may update their data at any time via the website, this includes requesting that their data be deleted. 

Deleted records will be marked as 'deleted' and are no longer made available to other registered users. These records will be retained for the maximum allowable period so that the relevant authorities can request them at their discretion. 

### Data we collect about your use of the website

Our webservers generate log files every time a page is accessed. This information is used by us to examine how our systems are performing and the level of service we are providing, the data is aggregated and does not identify an individual. 

This information includes :- 

  * The Internet address of the computer that requested the page. 
  * The name of page you accessed. 
  * The page element that was requested. 
  * The type of web browser you used. 
  * Any error messages. 

This information is used by us to examine how our systems are performing and the level of service we are providing, the data is aggregated and does not identify any individual.
